// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Question 1 ?" ,
    answer: "Option 3",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Option 2",
      "Option 3",
      "Option 4",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Question 2 ?" ,
    answer: "Option 1",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Option 2",
      "Option 3",
      "Option 4",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Question 3 ?" ,
    answer: "Option 3",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Option 2",
      "Option 3",
      "Option 4",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Question 4 ?" ,
    answer: "Option 1",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Option 2",
      "Option 3",
      "Option 4",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Question 5 ?" ,
    answer: "Option 4",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Option 2",
      "Option 3",
      "Option 4",
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Question 6 ?" ,
    answer: "Option 1",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Option 2",
      "Option 3",
      "Option 4",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Question 7 ?" ,
    answer: "Option 3",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Option 2",
      "Option 3",
      "Option 4",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Question 8 ?" ,
    answer: "Option 2",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Option 2",
      "Option 3",
      "Option 4",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Question 9 ?" ,
    answer: "Option 4",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Option 2",
      "Option 3",
      "Option 4",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Question 10 ?" ,
    answer: "Option 2",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "Option 2",
      "Option 3",
      "Option 4",
    ]
  },
];